这就是那位八卦女吗
Is that the Gossip?
不对  她是个荡妇
No, that's the Slut.
她不是荡妇  她很会调情
She's not a slut. She's a flirt.
她和真人秀上的几个男人发生过关系
How many guys on the show has she hooked up with?
节目里有多少男的
How many guys are on the show?
戴着那副眼镜对她可没什么用
She's not gonna fool anyone with those glasses.
给  把这个交给戴安
Here. Bring this to Diane.
这是什么
What is it?
什么也不是
Nothing.
好吧  真人秀就是要"真实"
Okay,  reality, you know, as in "Real,"
就是"记录下你的所作所为"
as in "It happened and we just filmed it."
你的论点是真人秀就是真实发生的事
Your argument is that reality shows are actually real?
不  我的论点是我们对选手不加限制
No, my argument is that we don't control the cast.
他们做我们看
They behave and we observe.
记录发生的一切
They are as they appear.
-就像唐纳德・特朗普  -等等
- Just like Donald Trump. - Wait a minute,
他可没上过我们电视台的节目
he wasn't on our network.
打断一下  我们是回到正题上
That... Let's get back... Excuse me.
我们还是回到问题上来
Let's get back to the questioning.
拜托  拜托  梅兰妮
Please, please. Melanie.
你们节目把我们安排在那顶层公寓里
Your show put us in that penthouse.
给我们备了酒
It gave us alcohol,
还告诉我们节目要有情色内容
and it told us that ratings were dependent
才能提高收视率...
on us pushing the sexual content...
那么你们的确有做情色内容
So you did push the sexual content?
让她说完
Let her finish.
然后你们摄影师拍下了我被侵犯的画面
Then your cameramen kept filming while I was violated.
你们更在意节目效果
Your show was more interested in making good TV
而不是保护我
than protecting me.
这番讲话说的真好
Thank you for that excellent speech.
不是吧...
Come on...
我来问你  梅兰妮
Let me ask you this, Melanie.
照你所说  你被性侵了
You were violated, you say.
但是你不记得你被性侵过
But you don't remember you were violated
因为你当时意识模糊
because you also claimed you were unconscious?
我说过了  节目组给我们备了酒
As I said, the show gave us alcohol
-和一点食物  -那家伙是谁
- and very little food. - Who is that guy?
-我去查查看  -好
- I can find out. - Yes.
别  让杰去
No. Get Jay.
-我来吧  -你知道你被性侵的唯一原因
- I'm fine. - the only reason you know you were violated
是因为我们有个制片人停止了拍摄
was because one of our producers stopped the shooting.
那已经是第二天了
Not until the next day.
那你怎么不向布雷克索赔450万
So why aren't you suing Blake for $4.5 million?
他才是对你实施性侵的人  对吧
He was the cast member who violated you, right?
为什么要让我们承担责任
Why are we the ones so honored?
我觉得布雷克和我一样  是受害者
I think that Blake was a victim, just like me.
梅兰妮  他在你意识模糊时和你发生性行为
Melanie, he had sex with you while you were unconscious.
这不是你说的吗
That's what you claim.
我还是不懂为什么不把他抓起来
I'm still not sure why he's not in handcuffs.
作为女人  我就会这么做
As a woman, that's what I would want.
-但因为我们财力雄厚  所以  -反对
- But I guess we're the deep pockets here, so... - Objection.
你记得这份合同吗  克拉克女士
Do you recognize this contract, Ms. Clark?
记得
I do.
那...
And...
你能把这些标记出来的...
would you mind reading for me this...
读给我听
highlighted portion right there?
"选手确认了解本节目"
"Cast Member acknowledges that the Show,
"《欲动风城》..."
Chicago Penthouse..."
需要我帮你读完吗
Would you like me to finish?
这和上面写的不符
That is not what happened here.
"《欲动风城》不鼓励性行为..."
"Chicago Penthouse does not encourage sexual behavior..."
你们当然希望有性行为
Of course you encourage sexual behavior.
并对一切因选手间的行为
"and is not responsible for any emotional or bodily harm
造成的情感和身体伤害
"That results from engaging in such behavior
"不承担相应责任"
with fellow cast members."
他是谁
Who was that?
送外卖的  上错楼层了
Food delivery. He was on the wrong floor.
他的食物呢
Where was his food?
我不知道  在前台吧
I don't know. I think at reception?
要我去看看吗
Should I go check?
好
Yes.
你上季的表现真棒
Hey, you were great last season.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们拿不到450万的
You're not getting $4.5 million.
性行为是双方自愿的
The sex was consensual.
你听到的可不是这样
You just heard it wasn't.
不  我听到的是那女人事先准备好的话
No, what I just heard was a woman who was tightly scripted.
-你说笑吗  -"你们节目看着我被性侵"
- Seriously? - "Your show kept filming while I was violated."
梅兰妮可说不出这种话  拜托
Melanie does not talk like that. Come on.
也许在真人秀里说不出
Maybe not on your reality show,
毕竟她的人设是一个荡妇
where she's scripted to be a bimbo.
但在这里  她的人设就变成
Instead of here, where she's scripted
瓦莎学院的毕业生了吗
to be a Vassar post-grad student?
好吧  说说你开的条件
All right. What's your offer?
八万  算作删掉她那集的毙稿费...
80 grand. The kill fee for not showing the episo...
你知道这案子你们胜算不大吧
You know you have no case, right?
-不  你知道我们有什么吗  -什么
- No, you know what our case is? - What?
-你的恐惧  史蒂文斯女士  -不
- Your fear, Ms. Stevens. - Oh, no.
-我可惨了  -这份合同
- I'm really scared now. - This contract.
"你交出所有权利"
"You hand over all your rights,
"不能以任何理由提起诉讼"
and you can't sue for any reason"?
-业内合同都这样  -你们要为此付出代价
- All standard in the industry. - And that's why you'll pay.
你很怕我们在庭上攻击这份合同
You are scared to death we will rip this apart in court.
如果法官认为合同没有效力
If a judge throws out your contract,
节目台就得出这笔钱
reality TV has to play fair.
你别高估自己的能力
You have misread your power.
还有件事  史蒂文斯女士
Uh, one thing, Ms. Stevens.
你可以叫我安德莉亚
You can call me Andrea.
-安德莉亚  -什么事  阿德里安
- Andrea. - Yes, Adrian.
我们正式要求你们提供
Here's our official request for all the footage
案发当天的所有录像
from the day in question.
这是私有财产
That's proprietary.
要打赌吗
You want to bet?
乔什・布里克纳法官
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我没想到你们因过去一周发生的事
I didn't realize how much on edge you were with
都被弄得紧张兮兮的
what's been going on this past week.
有几位律师被杀
I mean, a couple of lawyers get killed,
你们都觉得自己会成为目标
and you all think that you have targets on your backs.
我本想把这些文件直接扔给你们  但是
I-I was gonna throw those files directly at you, but, uh,
我担心你们会吓破胆
I was afraid you'd wet yourselves.
布莱恩  你能帮我把文件捡起来吗
Brian, could you pick that up, please?
我可能还有用
I may need to use it again.
好了  现在  关于这个
All right, now, with respect to this
证据请求
evidentiary request,
谁能给我解释一下这些录像
could somebody please explain to me the footage
-以及相关情况  -好的  法官阁下
- and what's involved? - Yes, Your Honor,
这份材料是私有财产...
this material is proprietary...
录像是重要的...
The videotape is vital...
一个一个来
One at a time.
你先说
You. Go.
你好  法官阁下  安德莉亚・史蒂文斯
Hi, Your Honor. Andrea Stevens.
-很高兴见到你  -谢谢  彼此彼此
- Thrilled to meet you. - Oh, thank you. Likewise.
我们制片人拍摄的镜头
Uh, the footage shot by our producers
有些是非常私人的东西
is sometimes extremely personal.
这些私有材料不能被呈上法庭
This is proprietary material that shouldn't be casually exposed.
事实上  这可能会让我们选手
In fact, it could embarrass,
感到难为情...
potentially, our contestant, so...
这些选手同意让节目在30多个国家播出
These contestants agree to broadcast themselves over 30 countries.
但是现在因为诉讼的原因
But now that a lawsuit has been filed,
辩方却要保护他们的隐私
the defense wants to protect their privacy?
-这是个什么节目  -一个真人秀
- What is this show? - It is a reality show
名叫《欲动风城》
called Chicago Penthouse.
其中选手的目标
Oy. And the goal of the contestants
是在他们中选出自己的绝佳配偶
is to find a romantic match among the other contestants.
如果找不到  他们就得死吗
And if they don't, they get killed?
那就有意思了
That would be interesting.
-不  他们会被淘汰  -真刺激
- No, they get sent home. - Exhilarating.
好了  我来捋一下看我说的对不对
All right, let me see if I understand this thing correctly.
这里涉及到成堆的选手镜头
There's tons of footage of these contestants?
而且制片人有权
And the producers retain the right
播出任意或者全部镜头  对吗
to use any or all of this footage for broadcast? Is that right?
-没错  法官阁下  -没错  正是如此
- That is correct, Your Honor. - Yes, that's exactly correct.
而且  这堆录像里面就有
In fact... Yeah. And-and somewhere within all of this footage
涉嫌性侵的影片镜头
is evidence of an alleged assault?
-没错  -是的
- Correct. - Right.
那它们就属于
Well, that would be, uh,
关键物证  对吗
material evidence, now, wouldn't it?
不  其实  我觉得...
No, actually, what I think is that...
你知道我怎么想吗
You know what I think?
我觉得你  史蒂文斯女士
What I think is that you, Ms. Stevens,
应该把录像交给他们
should give them the tapes.
与此同时
And while you're at it,
法庭也需要一份拷贝
supply the court with duplicate copies.
马上
Pronto.
这是个法律术语
That's a legal term.
-好的  法官阁下  -好了
- Yes, Your Honor. - Okay. Well, uh,
我准备敲锤子了
I'm about to bang my gavel.
所以如果有人要钻到桌子底下找掩护
So if, uh, anybody wants to take cover under their desks,
现在是时候了
now's the time.
《欲动风城》
第14季  原片
这是录像证据大杂库
That's a video depo dump.
一整季的
The whole season.
十几个摄像机全天候录下来的
24-hour-a-day video from a dozen cameras.
而且他们没标时间没做加注就送过来了
And they sent them over with no time code or description.
全部过一遍得好几周的时间
It's gonna take weeks to go through all of it.
我愿意做
I'll do it.
你来决定
It's up to you.
#It's your birthday happy birthday, it's your birthday#
伙伴们  为第十四季干杯
Okay, guys! To season 14!
这是谢丽尔  蒂娜和约翰尼
Okay, that's Sheryl and Tina and Johnny.
穿运动背心的那个
The one in the tank top.
大家都讨厌他  因为他特阴险
Everybody hates him because he's a snake.
杀了我算了
Kill me now.
下一个  这段太早了
Next tape. This one's too early.
有一点我没明白
So here's what I don't understand.
你看着还算半个聪明人
You seem like a semi-half-intelligent person.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么还看这个
How can you watch this?
你喜欢橄榄球吧
You like football, right?
得了  你怎么能把这个跟橄榄球相提并论
Oh, come on, you can't equate this with football.
咱们来讨论一下慢性创伤性脑损伤
Let's talk about chronic traumatic head injuries.
我不是对节目里的人有意见
I'm not criticizing what happens to the people on the show.
我是对看这节目的观众有意见
I'm just criticizing what happens to the viewer.
你就没有负罪的快感吗
Don't you have a guilty pleasure?
你就不在油管上看男生跳冰的视频吗
Don't you watch YouTube videos of guys diving onto ice
或者看恐怖电影  漫画书之类的
or watch horror movies or read comic books?
你是说连环画小说吗
You mean graphic novels?
天啊  真的假的  这你还取笑我
Oh, my God. Seriously? And you make fun of me?
连环画小说是新兴文学
Graphic novels are a new literature.
对  跟斯坦贝克似的
Right. Like Steinbeck.
美国作家  曾获1962年诺贝尔文学奖
伪君子
What a hypocrite.
等下  就是这  这是最后一次总结场
Oh, wait. Wait, there. That-That's the last Wrap-Up Circle.
-你怎么知道  -他们在配对
- How do you know? - They're pairing up.
这是两个不同角度的摄像机拍的
These are two camera angles.
#It's your birthday#
你需要帮忙吗  小美女
You need some help, little lady?
这倒是能证实醉酒
Well, that confirms the drunkenness.
天啊  把泡泡机打开
Oh, my God, turn on the bubbles!
-我太喜欢飞机了  -等等
- I love jets! - Wait, wait, wait,
我没有泳衣
I don't have a-a swimsuit.
我连一件泳衣都没有
I don't even own a swimsuit.
#It's your birthday, happy birthday#
这可不妙
Okay. That's not good.
但这依然不代表同意
Well, it's still not consent.
这不是在公共台播的节目吗
Isn't this on network TV?
对  他们打马赛克了
Yeah. They pixelate it.
这一段会持续一阵子
Uh, this goes on for a while.
这算是同意了  她怂恿人家了
Now it's consent. She just instigated.
-停  -关机
- Cut it. - Cameras off.
他们为什么要藏着这个呢
Why are they hiding this?
如果这个对我们不利  他们为什么还要藏着
I mean, if it's not good for us, why are they hiding it?
可能是录像里的其它东西
It could be something else in the footage.
#It's your birthday#
我好无聊
I'm bored.
你抢我台词
That's my line.
大家都觉得我会进监狱
Everybody expected me to be in jail,
所以我没什么事可做
so I have nothing to do.
你去旁听你爸的提审吗
Are you going to your dad's arraignment?
不  我受够了
No. I think I'm done.
很奇怪  一年前  一切都很正常
It's weird. A year ago, everything was normal.
我们每年复活节都办聚会
We'd have a party every Easter.
你今年可以来我家过逾越节
Hey, you can come to my house for Pesach this year.
犹太教传统节日
我甚至还可以给你藏几个复活节彩蛋
I'll even hide a few Easter eggs for you.
我可是会接受你的邀请的
You know, I might take you up on that.
我们午餐应该不醉无归
We should get drunk at lunch.
这是我认识的你吗
Who are you?
另一个人了
A different person.
另一种风格的你
A different genre of person. Oh.
-怎么了  -不知道  感觉有点奇怪
- What? - I don't know. Feels a little weird.
糟糕
Shit.
杀死所有律师
傲骨之战
第二季 第三集
BY ABU 20180522
别动
Don't move.
我们可不想让这东西空气传播
We don't want it to go airborne.
等等  这...
Wait, what...
这是什么
what is this?
我不知道  可能是...
I don't know. It could be...
是什么  烘焙粉吗
What, baking powder?
不  太偏棕色了
No. Looks too brown.
"我破产了  老婆孩子都没了"
"I'm bankrupt. I've lost my wife. I've lost my kids.
"都是因为你"
All because of you."
要命  信里说这是蓖麻毒
Oh, fuck. It says it's ricin.
跟炭疽一样严重
Th-That's as bad as anthrax.
是的
Yes.
你能够着玻璃吗
Can you reach the glass?
能
Yeah.
不  别过来
No, no, no, no, no! Stay there!
这封信里面有蓖麻毒
There is ricin in this letter.
上面写着"杀死所有律师"
It says, "Kill all lawyers."
天啊
Oh, God.
跟另外那两个凶手一样
Just like the other two killers.
杰  疏散楼层
Jay, clear the floor.
我去报警
I'll call 911.
全体注意  离开这栋楼
Everyone, exit the building!
快点  快走  赶紧离开
Come on, let's go, let's go! Leave the floor now!
这不是演习  快点  快走
This is not a drill! Come on, let's go!
出去  快点  快走  起来
Out. Come on. Let's go. Get up, get up.
通知大家有疑似化学品威胁
Tell everyone there's a-a possible chemical threat.
起立  出去
Get up, get out!
快走  快走
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
-快点  -杰
- Come on. - Jay!
杰  告诉建筑工程师关掉暖通空调
Yo! Jay, tell the building engineer to turn off the HVAC!
好的  这就去  快走
Right. On it. Let's go, let's go, let's go. Come on.
我们呼吸要轻柔  以防万一
We should breathe lightly, just in case.
克丽丝滕  出什么事了
Kristen. What's wrong?
梅丽莎发现了一封信  恐吓信
Marissa found a letter. A threatening letter.
-客户寄来的吗  -寄给给戴安的
- From a client? - To Diane.
他们认为是蓖麻毒
They think it's ricin.
蓖麻毒
Ricin?
雷迪克&博斯曼&洛哈特律所
卢卡
Lucca.
别过来
Stay there.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
别动
Don't move.
卢卡  一小原子的这个东西你就没命了
Lucca, one tiny atom of this stuff, and you can be dead.
是的  如果你继续说话的话
Yes. And if you keep talking,
你就会把它吸进去
you're gonna breathe it in.
所以别说话
So shut up.
这个看着虽然不好看
Now, this isn't gonna look pretty.
紧急救援的来了
Emergency response is coming.
他们让你们别动
They don't want you to move.
他们担心你们会把孢子通过空气传播出去
They're worried you'll send the spores airborne.
谢谢  我们知道
Thanks. We know.
这个信封是哪儿来的
Where did the envelope come from?
戴安・洛哈特
没有邮戳
No stamps.
收发室
The mail room.
这不是演习
This isn't a drill!
疏散楼层
Clear the floor now!
快点
Come on, guys. Let's go.
借过
Excuse me. Excuse me.
-快点  -怎么了
- Come on, come on. - What's up?
快点  快走
Come on, come on. Let's go. Go, go, go, go.
天啊  杰
Oh, my... Jay! Jay!
我们遇上了疑似的化学品袭击
We have a possible chemical attack situation.
别碰你的脸  别碰你的衣服
Do not touch your faces, do not touch your clothes.
在楼梯下面等待应急救援
Wait at the base of the stairs for the emergency responders.
快走  快
Let's go! Come on!
出什么事了
What's going on?
疑似化学品袭击
Chemical scare.
什么  在哪
What? Where?
我们那层
Our floor.
客户寄来的吗
From a client?
我的客户之一
One of mine.
你老公在这
Your husband is here.
天啊  希望他们都没事
Oh, God, I hope they're being good.
他们刚...他们刚把空调关上
They just... they shut down the air conditioning,
然后我们做了疏散
and we evacuated.
好  让这些人在下面待着
Good, good. Hey, keep these people down here.
出现症状的人一概隔离
Isolate anyone who exhibits any symptoms.
危险物质小组马上就到
We've got the hazard material team going up now.
-上面还有我们的员工  -明白
- We still have employees up there. - I understand.
机动医疗组在路上了
A mobile medical team is on the way.
-你有空吗  -有
- Do you have a minute? - Y-Yeah.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
没事  我刚才不在  我去吃午饭了
Yeah. I-I wasn't here. I was at lunch.
那就好
All right, good.
That's good. Okay.
好了  搜到了  蓖麻毒
Okay, here it is. Ricin.
想听吗
Do you want to hear?
我也不知道  该听吗
I don't know. Do I?
"暴露于蓖麻毒后的一天到两个月之间"
"Symptoms can begin any time between one day and two months
"都可能出现症状"
after the exposure."
就跟验孕一样
Like a pregnancy test.
至少不用在棒棒上尿尿
At least we won't have to pee on a stick.
不好
Oh, no.
怎么了
What?
我觉得我要打喷嚏了
I think I'm gonna sneeze.
-别  -控制不了
- Don't. - It's involuntary.
把你的舌头顶在门牙处  有用的
Press your tongue between your front teeth. It works.
好了  奏效了
Okay, I think that did it.
要是我们没死  我今晚要喝个大醉
Oh, if we don't die, I'm gonna get so drunk tonight.
你们好  二位现在怎么样了
Hey there. How are you two doing?
挺好的
Really good.
雷&博&洛律所平常的一天
Just another day at Reddick, Boseman & Lockhart.
我叫德鲁・乐华图
So, I'm Drew Lovatto,
危险物质小组的
the Hazardous Materials Unit.
很高兴认识你  我是梅丽莎・戈德
Nice to meet you. Marissa Gold.
-玛娅  -你们好
- Maia. - Hey.
我们会非常缓慢地把这些全部处理掉  好吗
So, we're gonna take this all very slowly, okay?
你们有人出现了什么症状吗  呼吸困难
Now, do either of you have any symptoms-- trouble breathing,
咳嗽  皮肤过敏
coughing, skin irritations?
我差点就打喷嚏了  但我忍住了
I almost sneezed, but I've gotten it under control.
很好
Good.
我要先给你们戴上口罩
I'm gonna put these masks on your faces first.
用餐巾是个很好的主意
The napkins were a great idea.
大小合适吗
That a good fit?
很合适  能送给我吗
Perfect. Can I keep it?
当然  但不能用它来扮成黑武士
Sure. No Darth Vader impressions, though.
该死
Damn.
好  现在还不要动
Okay, now, don't move yet.
我看见粉末在桌子上
I see there's powder on the desk,
你的膝盖  胳膊和你的手上
your lap, your arm, and your hand--
还有别的地方有吗
is it anywhere else?
据我们所知没有了
Not that we can see.
首先  我先带你离开桌子  好吗
So first, I'm gonna move you away from the desk, okay?
我需要你
I'm gonna need you...
-梅丽莎  -梅丽莎
- Marissa. - Marissa.
我需要你  梅丽莎
I'm gonna need you, Marissa,
在一分钟内非常小心地站起来
to stand very carefully in one minute.
但是首先  我要先把你的椅子挪开  好吗
But first, I'm gonna roll you back away from the desk, okay?
好的
Okay.
好
现在
Now...
我要非常小心地把你膝盖上的粉末弄掉
I'm gonna get that powder out of your lap very carefully.
真的吗  我们一点也不熟
Really? We hardly know each other.
我会很温柔的
I'll be gentle.
我需要你非常小心地站起来  慢点
I need you to stand very carefully, very slowly.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
起身
And... stand.
很好  原地不动
Okay, good. Stay right here.
现在  我需要你
Now, I need you...
把手翻过来  把粉末倒进袋子
to turn your hand over, dump the powder in the bag.
你之前做过这个吗
You've done this before?
是的  一次
Yep. Once.
好了  现在我需要你们俩站进这些袋子
Okay. Now I need you both to step into these bags,
脱掉衣服  把衣服留在袋子底部
remove your clothes, leave them in the bottom of the bag.
-当着你的面吗  -我会转过身去
- In front of you? - I'll turn around.
你们把这些穿上
I'll need you both to put these on.
好了  德鲁
Done, Drew.
好了
Okay.
要是我们没事  我俩觉得该去大喝一场
If we survive this, we figured we should get drunk tonight.
你想来吗
You want to join us?
我们还是先确保安全
Let's focus on surviving this first.
失陪一下
Would you excuse me?
你刚才居然就这么约他了
Did you really just ask him out?
我知道  很怪异  对吗
I know. Weird, right?
要是我要死了
If I'm gonna die...
是苏打粉
Baking soda.
什么
What?
你不需要戴这个了
You do not need that.
我的老天爷
Oh... my God.
-就这样  -没错
- That's it? - Yup.
我就不打扰了
I'll get out of your hair.
通过一盒盒的苏打粉来拯救世界
Saving the world one box of baking soda at a time.
保重
You take care.
很高兴你们没死
I'm glad you didn't die.
那和我们一起去喝一杯吗
Hey, how about that drink?
去庆祝
You know, that celebratory...
"我们没死"的酒会
"We didn't die" drink.
听起来很有趣  但我要加班
Sounds fun, but I got to work late.
如果你改变心意
Well, if you change your mind...
我们八点钟会在楼下的酒吧
we're gonna be in the downstairs bar at 8.
知道了
Got it.
你还真是主动
Wow, you are forward.
"我破产了"
"I'm bankrupt.
证据
老婆跑了
"I've lost my wife,
孩子也没了
"I've lost my kids...
全都因为你
"All because of you.
你收了我很多钱  继续下个案子
"You overcharge me and go on to your next case.
这次你别想得逞
"Well, not this time.
你会像我一样受伤
"You're going to hurt just like me.
这是蓖麻毒
"This is ricin.
"就当做这是我的尾款"
Consider it in lieu of my last payment."
"当做"拼错了
"Lieu" is spelled L-O-O.
署名是"一位客户"
Signed "A Client."
我们会查上面的指纹
We'll run fingerprints on this,
但你们可以帮我做件事
but there's something you can do for me.
什么事
What?
我需要你们的客户名单
I need a list of your clients.
你知道我们不能那样做
You know we can't do that.
你也知道  嫌犯是你们的客户
Just so you know, the suspects are your clients,
或至少是洛哈特女士的客户
or at least Ms. Lockhart's clients,
不知道他们的身份我就帮不上忙
and I can't fully help you unless I know their identities.
伊恩
Ian...
我们的律师保密协议规定我们不能这样做
our attorney-client privilege prevents us from doing that.
而且理由很充分
And for really, really good reason.
我们的一些客户可能将来
Some of our clients might have future dealings
会和你的部门产生纠纷
with your department.
你们可以获取他们的同意
You can get permission from them.
写这封信的客户
Any client who wrote that letter
不会签同意书的
wouldn't agree to put their name on it.
正好可以缩小嫌犯的范围
And that would narrow down our suspects.
我们也不能把名字告诉你
Which we couldn't tell you.
有人要杀了你们
Look, someone is trying to kill you.
这可不是开玩笑
This is not a joke.
我是来帮你们的  我不是你们的敌人
I'm here to help; I am not your enemy.
但你们不配合我就帮不上忙
But I can't do anything unless you work with me.
你也明白的
You know that's true.
我们让警察调查客户的同时
We can't represent our clients at the same time
我们就不能代表他们了
that we're having the police investigate them.
非常合理
Yeah, everything makes sense.
我只知道你在司法部
Look, all I know is you were ten years
工作了十年
at the Department of Justice,
你一次也没让我操心过
and I didn't worry about you once,
你才来这一个月  就发生了这样的事
and you've been here for a month, and here we are.
现在是非常时期
It's an unusual time.
不  我不这么认为
No, I don't think it is.
我在做我想做的事
I'm doing what I want.
-注意安全  -好
- Stay safe. - Okay.
这下完了
This is fucked.
确实  但他说得对
It is-- but he's right.
我们不给他客户名单  他就帮不上忙
We can't give him the client names, he can't help us.
虽然我是新来的
Look, I'm new here,
但或许我们应该看看我们的收费标准
but maybe we should be looking at what we charge clients.
我们的收费标准
What we charge clients
和市里所有律所相比都有竞争力  莉兹
is competitive with every other law firm in town, Liz.
或许这就是客户对律师非常不满的原因
Which is maybe why clients are so angry with their lawyers.
你真的要责怪我们吗  我们才是受害者
Are you really blaming us? We're the victims here.
得了吧  我们离受害者还很远
Oh, come on, we are far from victims.
为什么我们不
Why don't I do some research
调查一下戴安的客户
into Diane's clients?
有多少来着
How many are there?
43名
Uh, 43.
他们当中有没有不满意我们的收费
Any of them upset about our billing
或是不满意输了官司之类的
or losing a case or whatever?
好吧
Yeah, right.
我去警局那里把信取回来
Look, I'll get the letter back from the police
再拿它和别的信对比一下
and compare it to other correspondences.
昨天这儿来了个奇怪的人
There was somebody here yesterday.
胡须男  送外卖的
A bearded man, delivering food.
梅丽莎昨天和他说过话
Marissa talked to him.
我会及时向你更新情况
I'll keep you updated.
现在我们要打电话给
Now, we need to get back on the phone
安德莉亚・斯蒂文斯
with Andrea Stevens.
我不想让他们觉得我们在示弱
We don't want to be seen as being weak here.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好
Oh, yeah.
还想当糕点师吗
Yeah? Still want to become a pastry chef?
真是越想越有吸引力了
It's looking more and more appealing.
有什么我能帮你的吗
Is there anything I can do?
不用了  我就是...需要摆脱这件事
No, I just... I just have to shake this off.
为什么不回家休息
Why don't you go home?
下午休息吧
Take the afternoon.
你刚经历了疑似蓖麻毒的袭击
If there's ever a day you could take a break,
实在是放假的最佳理由了
it's after a ricin scare.
待会吧  我没事  我还要采集证词
I mean, maybe later. I'm good. I have the depo.
我帮你做
I'll handle it.
去吧
Go.
他真的只是来送餐
He really was just delivering food.
今天的事和他没关系
He had nothing to do with this.
戴安有点多疑了
Diane's getting a little paranoid.
也是有原因的  你看起来不错啊
With good reason. You seem good.
是啊  这类事件我应付自如
Yeah. I tend to rise to these occasions.
你有没有问收发室
Are you questioning the mail room?
这就去
Next stop.
我帮你
Can I help?
不用了  你去继续盯真人秀镜头吧
No. You take the reality show footage.
我这就去
I'm on it.
屋里站满了警察
I had wall-to-wall cops in here.
他们把我的整个系统都打乱了
They messed up my whole system.
我又要花三四个小时才能赶回原来的进度
It's gonna take me three, four hours just to get caught up.
这是什么
What's this?
恐吓信封是从这里送出的
The threatening envelope came inside.
应该是由人亲手交送到这儿
Looks like it was hand-delivered here,
然后你的人把信送进了戴安的办公室
then one of your guys brought it up to Diane's office.
不会是我的人
Wasn't one of my guys.
不是所有信都先送到收发室吗
Doesn't everything go through the mail room?
从外面送来的信是
Everything from the outside.
这封信既没有署名  也没有时间戳
This doesn't have a signature, no time stamp.
信是从这栋楼里送出的
This came from inside the building.
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh,
太遗憾了
I am so sorry.
我听说了
I heard.
-听说什么了  -听说你们遇到麻烦了
- About? - About your troubles here.
看起来你们树敌了  是吧
I mean, it seems like you have some enemies, huh?
如果能帮你的话  我们就别打这场官司了
If it helps, we could take this case off your plate,
只要达成协议就好
come to some sort of settlement.
好啊
Sure.
430万
$4.3 million.
不是我想的那个数字
Mm, not quite what I had in mind.
但是  等等  九万五千倒是可以
But 95... no, $95,000 would do it.
你们不会想
Listen, you don't want to have
再多一个对你们不满的客户吧
another unhappy client on your hands, do you?
我们开始吧
Shall we?
莉兹
Liz.
你来干什么
What are you doing?
戴安让我来  她觉得她有点应付不来
Oh. Diane asked me to sit in. She's not feeling up to it.
好吧
Yeah.
你口渴吗  要我拿点东西给你喝吗
Are you thirsty? Can I get you something to drink,
好啊
Yeah.
-或者不喝东西了  你懂吗  -不是很懂
- maybe, or... or maybe not, you know? - I really don't know.
这段视频是在哪拍的
Where was this video taken?
这是顶层公寓的吧台
It was at the bar at the penthouse.
他们相处得挺融洽的  是吧
They look pretty comfortable with each other, don't they?
你这是针对梅兰妮心理状态的推测
That is speculation about Melanie's state of mind,
而且距离侵犯发生还有好几个小时
hours before the assault took place.
涉嫌侵犯
Alleged assault.
你知道现在法官不在席吧
And you know there's no judge here, right?
我只是将我的反对记录在案
I'm just preserving the objection for the record.
当然  请记下来
Of course. Preserved.
在这场三点发生的邂逅后和下一场开始前
Did you speak with Melanie after this 3:00 encounter,
你有没有和梅兰妮说过话
but before the later one?
我做了一个OTF
I conducted an OTF.
解释一下
And what is that?
就是"即兴速访"
That's an "On the fly" interview.
我和布雷克玩得很开心
I had a great time with Blake.
我感觉你和布雷克之间有化学反应
Yeah, I'm sensing that you and Blake have good chemistry.
你可以说我们相处得很好
Yeah, you could say we're getting along.
抱歉  打断一下  请说他的名字
Sorry, sorry. Uh, use his name, please.
该死
Shit.
我和布雷克之间有化学反应
Blake and I have great chemistry.
他看起来也很开心
He seems down to have a good time.
他绝对是那个让我想认真相处的人
Definitely someone to spend some quality time with.
所以  你像摆弄木偶一样摆弄我们的客户
So, you're turning our client into a puppet,
然后还怪她
and then you blame her?
我的天
Oh, my God.
-怎么了  -我从视频里找到了有用的东西
- What's wrong? - I found something in the video.
我要饿死了  我们待会再谈不行吗
I'm starving. Can we talk about this later?
我都不知道你到底要我怎样
I don't even get what you're asking me.
我觉得你非常清楚我在说什么
Oh, I think you know exactly what I'm saying.
梅兰妮  你确实说了该说的
I mean, Melanie, you talk the talk,
-但我不知道  -我不懂你的意思
- but I don't know. - I don't understand.
亲爱的  你的话语片段确实不错
You give a good sound bite, honey,
但是电视节目是视觉媒体
but TV is a visual medium.
我需要有影像来支撑
I need the video to back that up.
你不觉得这已经很有看点了吗
You don't think that this is visual?
你的上衣就是问题的所在之处
Now, that top sums up the problem.
你是个相机挑逗者  梅兰妮
You are a camera tease, Melanie.
梅兰妮  你还想继续拍吗
Melanie, you want to stay on the show?
那你得秀出点东西来
Then you gotta show us something.
你这话什么意思
What did you mean by that?
我的意思就是
I just meant that, uh...
她话说得很满  但是
You know, she was talking a very big game, but, uh,
在现实中  她并不够
in reality, she-- she wasn't exactly...
-风骚吗  -容我打断一下
- Putting out? - Excuse me,
她是谁
who is that?
我们的调查员
One of our investigators.
能不能请她不要质问我的客户
Could you ask her not to question my client, please?
当然  只要你的客户
Sure. As soon as your client
好好回答问题
starts answering the questions.
大家都知道
Look, everybody knows that
我们节目的收视率不稳定
our show's ratings go up or down
都取决于有没有挑逗性内容
based on us being provocative.
这并不意味着我们容忍强奸
That does not mean that we condone rape.
用词很重啊
Strong words.
抱歉打断一下  我确实很疑惑
I'm sorry, I'm really confused here.
我以为你们的论点是
I thought your whole argument
你们的客户失去意识
was that she was unconscious.
现在你们开始争辩是我们强迫她脱衣
Now you're arguing that we forced her to strip
并接受口交  我很困惑
and receive oral sex. I'm just... confused.
求你了  我饿死了  给我个三明治也行
Please, I'm starving. Can I even get a sandwich?
总结场完了之后就可以吃
Yes, after the Wrap-Up.
看  他们已经摆好龙舌兰自助宴了
But look, they just put out the tequila buffet.
龙舌兰自助宴  是什么
So, what is-- what is the tequila buffet?
我们所有的
Well, all our--
所有的参与者都知道我们有这个自助宴
all our contestants know that we had that.
我知道  但这到底是什么  我就是好奇
Yeah, but what-- what is it? I'm just curious.
就是摆了十几种高档龙舌兰酒的自助宴
It's a-about a dozen different high-end tequilas,
为了作比较用
for comparison's sake.
但他们都六小时没吃饭
And no food for six hours?
就只喝龙舌兰
Just shots of tequila?
我们没做错什么
Look, we haven't done anything wrong.
这是节目的传统
This is show tradition.
对啊  我们也没强迫
Yes, and we're not forcing
参与者喝  所以就这样吧
the contestants to drink, so please.
这环节是第15季的一部分吗
Is it part of season 15?
抱歉  你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
如果你没做错什么
If you did nothing wrong,
那么龙舌兰自助宴是第15季的一部分吗
is the tequila buffet part of season 15?
不是
No.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好
Hello?
戴安  我是杰・迪佩西亚
Diane, it's Jay Dipersia.
-你有时间吗  -有
- Do you have one second? - Sure.
你有没有客户在我们这栋楼里工作
Do any of your clients have offices inside the building?
我们这栋楼吗  为什么这么问
Our building? Why?
我问了收发室的人  但是这封信
I spoke to the mail room, but the letter sent to you
是从这栋楼里寄来的
came from inside the building.
好吧  有
Well, there's, um...
有个房地产公司  我们给他们做税务工作
a real estate firm-- we did taxes with them.
还有  一个科技创业公司
And, um, yeah, a tech start-up.
他们的执行总裁叫艾力克・克莱顿
The, uh, CEO, Alec Crichton.
他的离婚案是我们经手的
We handled his divorce.
好
Okay, good.
跟他俩有过争执吗
Any issues with either of them?
没  记忆中没有过
No, not that I remember.
离婚案后来的气氛不太好
The divorce, of course, got heated.
他失去了孩子的抚养权吗
Well, he lose custody of his kids?
是的
Yes.
好
Okay.
我会去问问  如果你想起什么记得说
I'll question them. If anything occurs to you, call me.
好  再见
Um, yeah. Good-bye.
行吧
All right.
分担花费政府补贴为奥巴马医保中的条款
在政府停止发放分担花费补贴后
President Trump has defended his decision
特朗普总统为该决议辩护
to end cost-sharing reduction subsidies
声明股价的涨...
by pointing to stock price gains...
执行制作人  埃尔维斯・哈利德
前传的想法
The idea of a... A prequel
直到我找到另一种切入的方式
just didn't interest me,
才激起我的兴趣
until I found another way in.
只要你是警探  就可以为所欲为
When you're a detective, you can do anything.
奸淫掳掠  为所欲为
Grab 'em by the pussy. Anything.
很多人以为这是在说特朗普
And a lot of people think it's about Trump.
《骄阳前的黑暗》
执行制作人  埃尔维斯・哈利德
但其实是说某种心理状态
But it's really about a certain mindset.
纽约臭气熏天  我要做大清洗
New York's a swamp, and I'm cleaning it up.
#与魔鬼同行#
#With the devil I ride#
#With the devil I ride...#
这将是将军肚小猪
This will be the third week
住在地图室的第三周了
the potbellied pig occupies the Map Room.
将军肚小猪进驻白宫地图室
虽然总统坚称皮蒂小猪
Though the president insists Petey the Pig
是有益的消遣  许多评论员担心
is a welcome distraction, many critics worry
小猪有损白宫声誉
the animal debases the office of the presidency.
我们想听听您的意见
We want to hear from you.
总统是否应该在白宫地图室收养小猪
Should the president keep a pig in the White House Map Room?
上网...
Go online...
我喜欢她  她只是直话直说
Uh, I like her. She just says what she thinks.
我知道  但你信任她吗
Eh, I know. But do you trust her?
我不知道  这重要吗
Uh, I don't know. Does that matter?
我又不娶她
I'm not gonna marry her.
老天爷  你能想象他俩的婚姻吗
My God, can you imagine that marriage?
莉兹和博斯曼
Liz and Boseman?
他们到底看上对方哪一点了
What did they even see in each other?
谁知道
I don't know.
也许是喜欢危险属性
Probably danger.
今天他称我为他的调查员
He called me one of his investigators today.
谁  博斯曼吗
Who, Boseman? Mm-hmm.
或者像我这样直呼其名  阿德里安
Or as I call him, Adrian.
-棒  -感觉他和我的关系更近了
- Nice. - I think we're getting closer, he and I.
我是说  他现在记得我的名字了
And by that, I mean he knows my name now.
干杯
I will drink to that.
咱俩心情这么好真奇怪
It's odd that we're in such a good mood,
考虑到今天差点没命
given that we were almost killed today.
我们是活在危险中的一代
Well, we're the generation of living dangerously.
你们还在这儿
You're still here!
-德鲁  -德鲁
- Drew! - Drew!
天啊  你俩喝醉了
God, you guys are sloshed.
没  没有
No! No.
我们只是见到你太高兴了
We are just really happy to see you.
-见我还活着  -没错
- Alive? - Yes!
-没错  -没错
- Yes! - Yes!
来坐
Here, sit, sit.
高脚凳
These are tall chairs.
你俩在喝什么
Uh, what are you drinking?
-酸威士忌  -不只一杯
- Whiskey sours. - More than one sour.
绝不是一杯
Not a singular sour.
好
Okay.
-再来一杯  -好的
- One more? - All right.
话说...
So...
糟糕
Oh, shit.
怎么了
What?
我要你跟我去趟洗手间
I need you to come with me to the bathroom.
现在吗
Now?
是的
Yes.
别走开
Don't leave.
-怎么了  -过来
- Why? Why? - Come here.
锁不上  这样靠着门吧
Oh, there's no lock. Here, just lean against the door.
他是为你来的
He's here for you.
-什么  -他是来看你的
- What? - He's here to see you.
-不是  -真的  是你请他来的
- No! - Yes. You invited him tonight.
-没错  但是...  -等等  去你的
- Yeah, but for... - Wait! Fuck you!
我是为你请的  我对他又没兴趣
I invited him for you. I'm not interested in him.
我知道  但他并不知道
Yeah, I know. But he doesn't know that.
好吧  要我回家吗
Okay, well, uh, do I go home?
不  我不想你走  我们正玩得开心
No. No, I don't want you to. We're having fun.
那我怎么做
Then what do I do?
暗示一下你是同性恋
Hint that you're gay.
什么
What?
-怎么暗示  -不知道
- How do I do that? - I don't know.
-天啊  我要回去喝酒了  -别走
- Oh, my God. I am going back to the bar. - No!
-让开  -玛娅
- Out of the way. - Maia!
等等
Wait!
-嗨  -我又点了两杯
- Hi. - Hey. I ordered you two more.
每人两杯吗
Two more each?
不  那样的话太不负责任了
No. That would be irresponsible.
我是同性恋
I'm gay.
我该...
What should I...
说什么
say? Uh...
恭喜
Congratulations.
我们不是一对
We're not gay. Not the two of us.
只有我是同性恋
I'm just gay.
你真的好帅
You're really handsome.
天啊  行了  我要回家了
Oh, my... Okay, i'm gonna go home.
别走  留下来
No, no, stay.
咱们都别走
We should all stay. Hey.
你们要来点猛的吗
You guys want something harder?
没错  我受冒犯了  我没强奸她
Yes, I'm offended! I didn't rape her.
-你怎么不说实话  梅兰妮  -麻烦你
- Why don't you tell the truth, Melanie? - Please,
克制住不要与我当事人对话
refrain from addressing my client.
你可以请你当事人出去避嫌
You could always ask your client to step out.
我要在现场
I want to be here for this.
布雷克  你为什么离开
Okay. Blake, why did you leave season 14
《欲动风城》第14季
of Chicago Penthouse?
因为她说我侵犯了她
Because she said I assaulted her,
制作人就淘汰我出局了
and then the producers kicked me off.
你与克拉克女士有过性接触吗
Did you have any sexual contact with Ms. Clark?
有过  但她是乐意的  我发誓
Yes, but she was into it. I swear to God,
我不是那种会硬取的人
I am not the kind of guy who does something like that.
所以性交是双方认可的
So the sexual contact was consensual?
是  梅兰妮问我要不要打一炮
Yeah. Melanie asked me if I wanted a surefire way
确保晋级最终一轮  我说当然好
to make it to the final round. I said sure.
我又不傻  我很努力在做节目
I mean, I'm not stupid. I'm trying to up my brand.
-性交是她的主意  -百分百她的主意
- The sex was her idea? - 100%.
她知道如何高调做戏
She knew how to make a spectacle,
那样的话就意味着更多的节目时间
and she knew that would mean more camera time.
你知道让我生气的是什么吗
You know what pisses me off?
我没有指控你  布雷克
I'm not accusing you, Blake.
我没有做错什么
I did not do anything wrong.
是你对我紧追不舍  梅兰妮
You were all over me, Melanie.
是你拉我进热浴缸的
You pulled me into that hot tub.
是醉酒后发生的
It was a drunken hookup.
而我对此毫无记忆
And I have zero memory of that.
-我记得  -这才是重点
- Well, I do. - That's the whole point.
行了  够了
Okay, okay, okay. Enough.
没事  听着...
No, it's all right. Look...
你没有把我灌醉
You didn't get me drunk.
你没有给我下药
You didn't drug me.
你没有把我按住  强取强攻
You didn't hold me down and force yourself on me.
我也没有拒绝你
And I didn't say no.
但某一时刻  我失去了拒绝的能力
But at some point, I lost the ability to say no.
你的问题是
And your problem is you're so sure
你确信自己不是那种男人  但却没意识到
you're not one of those guys that you fail to realize that,
在那天  那个时刻
on that day, in that moment,
你完成了那件你认为是我挑起的事
you decided to finish what you thought I had started.
你就成为了那种男人  布雷克
You became one of those guys, Blake.
是  我听说了
Yeah, I heard about that.
老天爷  炭疽
Jesus. Anthrax.
你们都还好吧
You guys all right up there?
没事  说是蓖麻毒
Yeah. Ricin.
只是吓唬人的
Just a scare.
我知道你是戴安的客户
I understand you're one of Diane's clients.
对啊
Oh, yeah.
那个愚蠢的贱人
That stupid bitch.
什么
Excuse me?
不  我不是说戴安
No, not Diane.
她是个好人
She's a sweetheart.
我是指我的前妻
No, my ex-wife.
就是因为她  我才需要戴安的
She's the reason I needed Diane.
帅
Cool.
这是什么
What is it?
我还不怎么清楚
Oh. I don't know yet, you know?
还在试着...理清思路
It's still trying to... become something.
我得先写下来才知道自己在想什么
I don't know what I'm thinking until I write it down.
都是你写的吗
This is all your writing?
对  看着像连环杀手对吧
Yeah. Looks like a serial killer, doesn't it?
没错
Yep.
洛莉・阿克曼
Lori Akerman.
我以前是《欲动风城》的制片人
I was a production manager on Chicago Penthouse.
以前吗  你为什么会被解雇
You were? And why were you fired?
因为我看见了我认为是
Because I saw what I thought
未经双方一致同意的性行为
was nonconsensual sex,
然后我停止了拍摄
and I shut down the production.
这个解雇理由挺奇怪的
That seems like a strange reason to fire you.
史蒂文斯女士说得像是
Ms. Stevens makes it sound like
节目只是尽职尽责
the show was just being responsible.
但我现在失业了
And yet here I am, out of work.
我觉得其中有误解
I think there's a misunderstanding here.
你被解雇不是因为
You were not let go because you...
史蒂文斯女士  别这样
Ms. Stevens, please.
你看见了什么让你担忧的事
What did you see that concerned you?
梅兰妮当时的精神状态
Melanie was in no state of mind
根本无法做出任何决定
to be making any kind of decisions,
更别说发生性行为的决定了
much less sexual ones.
她几乎是神志不清的
She was barely conscious.
那你当时为什么不阻止呢
And why didn't you stop it at the time?
我在和另一些参赛选手做采访
I was doing interviews with other cast members.
我知道梅兰妮喝醉了  但是我以为
I knew Melanie was drunk, but I thought
她和布雷克那时候已经被分开了
that she and Blake had separated by then.
没有其他问题了
No further questions.
阿克曼女士
Ms. Akerman, uh,
首先我对你现在的无业状态表示遗憾
first of all, I am so sorry about your unemployed state.
谢谢
Thank you.
你以前有过多少次
How many prior production
节目暂停拍摄的经历呢
shutdowns have you been involved in?
这是第一次
This was my first.
在《欲动风城》之前
And prior to, uh, Chicago Penthouse,
你在《德通纳海滩》
you worked on Daytona Beach
和《月夜宿舍》工作过
and Dorm Room Afterdark?
-对  -所以《欲动风城》发生了什么
- Yes. - So, what happened on Chicago Penthouse
比其他节目更糟糕的事情呢
that was worse than those other shows?
我说过了
I already said.
不是双方同意的性行为
Non-consensual sex.
我明白了
I see.
你对布雷克・马斯特占了节目的
And how did you feel about Blake Masters taking
主角戏份有什么感受
a prominent role on the show?
我
I...
-我有什么感受  -对
- How did I feel? - Yes.
你不是觉得他不是合适的选角吗
Didn't you disapprove of his casting?
没错
No.
节目里没有非裔女性选手
There were no African-American female contestants on the show.
对吗
Is that correct?
我不参与选角
I am not involved in casting.
你不担心节目里会有
You weren't concerned about depicting
-太多跨种族恋爱关系吗  -不
- too many interracial relationships? - No.
这里是几位《欲动风城》的
Here are some affidavits from several producers
制作人的宣誓书
on Chicago Penthouse
里面指出你明确表达过
attesting that you were expressly concerned
对跨种族恋爱
about the prevalence
盛行的担忧
of interracial relationships.
-反对  -真的吗  为什么
- Objection. - Really? Why?
-和本案无关  -事实上我猜
- Relevance. - Actually, my guess is
你是害怕这个问题太有关了
you're worried this is very relevant.
你是把我的话断章取义
You're taking me out of context.
我是在说观众的看法
I was talking about audience perception.
-我不种族歧视  -女士  你停止拍摄
- I'm not a racist. - Ma'am, didn't you shut down
是因为布雷克是黑人
the show because Blake was black
而梅兰妮是白人对吗
and Melanie was white?
-不是  -所以你允许白人选手之间
- No. - And this is why you allowed drunken sex
酒后性交  而不允许跨种族发生同样的事
between white cast members and not interracial.
那是什么
What's that?
一个测验
A test.
你找到什么了吗
Find anything?
暂时没有  你呢
Not yet. You?
可能有
Maybe.
这可真是侦探工作啊
This is the real detective stuff, huh?
每台打印机和复印机都会在印出的每一页
Every printer and copy machine leaves a unique signature
留下特有的微点印记
of microdots on every page it prints.
就像是那台打印机的指纹
Like, a fingerprint for that printer.
这张是你打开那封信的印记
Here's the one on the letter you opened.
这两张是从这栋楼里
Now, these are two printed pages
戴安的客户们那儿拿来的
from Diane's clients in the building.
我们看看信是不是从他们的打印机出来的
So we'll see if the letter came from their printers.
第一张是房地产客户的
First, the real estate client.
不吻合
No match.
另一张
Now the other one.
该死
Damn.
我以为会是房地产那家伙做的
I thought it would be the real estate guy.
可能他是在家里打印的
Maybe he printed it at home.
也可能是在打印店弄的
Or at a copy store.
又或者他不止有一台打印机
Or maybe he has more than one printer.
好吧  祝你好运
Okay, good luck.
你在做什么
Hey, what are you doing?
有第三个摄像头
There was a third camera.
看  这是第二天的录像
Look, this is from the next day.
浴缸上方有个锁定的摄像头
There's a locked-off camera above the hot tub.
喂  你怎么一点都不激动
Uh, hello? Why aren't you excited?
激动
I am.
信是从这层楼打印的
It's from this floor.
-什么  -给戴安的信
- What? - U-Uh, the letter to Diane?
不是这栋楼的客户打的
It's not from a client in this building,
那人就在这个办公室
it's from this office.
你怎么就不能让我秀一下
Why can't you let me have my moment?
你为什么要让我出洋相
Why do you have to show me up?
有第三个摄像头记录了侵犯事件
There was a third camera recording the assault,
-法官阁下  -是涉嫌侵犯  法官阁下
- Your Honor... - Alleged assault, Your Honor.
辩方没有把证据交出来
And the defense has failed to turn it over.
乔什・布里克纳法官
你知道我有什么搞不懂吗
You know what I don't understand?
西蒙和维罗妮卡之间发生了什么
What happened to Simon and Veronica?
他们一季下来发展得
I-I mean, they were getting so close
那么亲密  然后却完全没有下文
during the season, and then, nothing.
有什么合理解释吗
I-I mean, uh, does that ever get explained?
我不确定  法官阁下  但如果你想的话
I'm not sure, Your Honor, but I can ask the producers for you,
我可以帮你问一下制作人
if you'd like me to.
还有科特妮
A-And Courtney.
她为什么会被淘汰
I mean, why did she get expelled?
完全就不符合逻辑
It makes no sense.
-她是好人  -法官阁下
- She was the nice one. - Your Honor,
丢失的录像
the missing footage.
没错
Right.
史蒂文斯女士
Ms. Stevens?
录像在哪里
Where is it?
不好意思
I'm sorry?
我下的证据开示令是没写清楚吗
Did I not make my discovery order clear?
好的  这季开始制作人们决定
Oh, um, right. Uh, the producers decided against
停止使用偷拍的录像
using the spy cam footage this season,
所以他们忘记了它的存在
and they forgot it was even there.
没错  人之常情嘛
Right. Yeah, that could happen to anybody.
找出来
Find them.
立刻
Now.
是的  法官阁下
Yes, Your Honor.
谢谢  法官阁下
Thank you, Your Honor.
你是怎么了
What's the matter with you?
我做出了有利你们的裁决
I just ruled in your favor.
连个微笑都没有吗
Don't I even get a smile?
什么  法官阁下
Excuse me, Your Honor?
我的意思是
I mean...
你应该多点微笑
you should smile more.
我都不知道是从哪时起
Yeah, I don't-I don't know when it happened,
女人都不笑了
that women stopped smiling.
什么  这什么意思
What? What is this?
这算什么
What-what is it?
她在做什么
What is she doing?
你的协理律师在大笑
Uh, your co-counsel is laughing.
我错过什么了吗
Is-- am I missing something here?
没有  法官阁下
No, Your Honor.
我们最近要应付的事情太多了
We've been stretched really thin, recently.
是
Oh, right.
我听说了苏打粉恐慌那事
I heard about that whole baking soda scare.
-戴安  -对  谢谢
- Diane. Diane, Diane. - Yeah, thank you.
谢谢  法官阁下
Thank you, Your Honor.
她没事吧
I-Is she all right?
她就是喜出望外了  法官阁下
She's just pleasantly surprised, Your Honor.
刑事法庭
你没事吧
Uh, are you okay?
我吗
Am I?
没事  怎么了
Yes. Why?
你刚才在里面大笑
You were laughing in there.
是啊  法官太搞笑了
Yes, the judge was funny.
天啊
Oh, God.
你还在小剂量嗑致幻蘑菇吗
Are you still microdosing?
没有
Nope.
我不用它的时候就这样
This is what I'm like when I'm not.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
总统有没有把将军肚小猪
Listen, did the president put a potbellied pig
放在白宫地图室
in the White House Map Room?
你说什么
Uh, excuse me?
不  今天有没有一条关于特朗普
No, was there a story today
领养了一头叫皮蒂的猪
about Trump adopting a pig named Petey,
并把它放在白宫的新闻
and keeping him in the White House?
我...没有
I... No.
你看我的样子就像我是个疯子
You're looking at me like that's insane.
你好
Hi.
你想找我聊聊吗
You wanted to talk to me?
是的
Yes. Uh...
我们的无线网络会记录律所人员的登出时间
so our Wi-Fi keeps track of when people in the firm log out.
我们在同一个服务器上
We're all in the same server.
-你知道这点吗  -不知道
- Did you know that? - No.
-这是你的身份识别码  -好吧
- See, that's your I.D. Number. - Okay.
它显示昨天上午10点23分
It shows, at 10:23 a.m. yesterday,
你是最后一个登出的人
you were the very last one to log out.
说得通
Yeah. Makes sense.
我们在兰提莫斯一案的案情简报上滞后了
We're behind on the Lanthimos brief,
我中午都在工作  很晚才走
and I've been working through lunch, and pretty late.
对  但你看  其他人都登出了
Right, but you see, everyone else logged out
当然是因为有疑似化学物的袭击
because, of course, there was a chemical scare,
我们都离开了这栋大楼
and we all left the building.
那我想我忘了登出了
Well, I guess I forgot to log out.
不  你是自动登出的
No, you're logged out automatically.
你就是比其他人都晚离开
Uh, you just stayed later than everyone.
正如我说的
Well, like I said,
我的工作滞后很多了
I've-I've been pretty behind.
你为什么不怕蓖麻毒
Why weren't you afraid of the ricin?
最后证明了不是蓖麻毒
It turns out, it wasn't ricin.
对
Right.
但事先没人知道
But no one knew that.
信是你送给戴安的  对吗
You sent the letter to Diane, didn't you?
我不知道你在说什么
I-I don't know what you're...
事情是这样的
Here's the thing.
你要进监狱
You're going to jail.
不  我
No, I...
你会去
Yes.
除非你跟戴安道歉
Unless you go apologize to Diane.
告诉我你为什么这么做
Tell me why you did it.
工作太多了
There's been so much work.
而且
And...
他们在周五就要案情陈述
they wanted the brief in on Friday,
我没法及时写完
and I can't get it in on time.
我很害怕会被炒掉  我就想多要一天
I... I was so afraid of being fired, I just wanted a day.
好
Okay.
我还需要你签份东西
Uh, I-I just need you to sign something.
-太无情了  -什么
- That was cold. - What?
告诉他要么签字  要么你就向警察告发他
Telling him to sign or you'd turn him over to the cops,
然后你还是向警察告发了他
then, you turned him over to the cops.
我又不给他干活
I don't work for him.
我给律所干活
I work for the firm.
要我看什么
What am I looking for?
她晕过去了
She passed out.
我认为你会想
Oh, I think you're gonna want to...
看这个部分的  史蒂文斯女士
want to watch this part, Ms. Stevens.
安德莉亚
Andrea.
这就是高潮部分
And here's where it gets exciting.
要么收下要么上庭
Take it or leave it.
我得到的授权最多就是这个数
I'm not authorized to go any higher.
将军肚小猪  特朗普
回车
删除
320万
$3.2 million.
太好了
All right.
你听说了吗
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Did you hear?
-什么  -特朗普要在白宫
- What? - Trump is keeping a potbellied pig
养只将军肚小猪吗
in the White House?
不是  戴安
No, Diane.
迪佩西亚  他抓到了那个
Dipersia, he caught the fellow
给你送恐吓信的人
who sent you that threatening letter.
谁
Who?
我们律所的一个律师
One of our associates here.
想要更多时间来写案情简要
Wanted more time to write his brief.
不是吧
No.
他的案情简要
His brief...
戴安
Diane.
你没事吧
You all right?
听着
Look, look, um...
我知道最近几周过得很艰难
I know the last few weeks have been hard.
但你对离开法律这行是认真的吗
But are you really serious about leaving the law?
我什么
Am I what?
离开法律这行是认真的
Serious about leaving the law.
莉兹说你很难接受
Liz said you've been having some difficulty
卡尔的死
with Carl's death, and...
和那些模仿谋杀
these copycat killings.
是真的吗
Really?
不  我没事
No, I'm good.
很好
Good.
我们不能再失去你了
We can't afford to lose you, too.
阿德里安  过去的几周
Adrian, these last few weeks,
感觉死亡无处不在
it felt like death was everywhere.
仅此而已
That's all.
但现在
But now...
你又看到生命的希望了
You're seeing life again.
不  我只是不在乎了
No. I just don't care.
田纳西・威廉斯[美国小说家]怎么说的来着
What did Tennessee Williams say?
"幸福的秘密是什么"
"What is the secret to happiness?
"糊涂"
Insensitivity."
我就有这样的感觉
That's what I feel.
无论如何  干得好
Well, good job, anyway.
我们又多赚了60万
We are $600,000 richer.
有了特朗普  不会被扣那么多税了
And with Trump, we won't be taxed as much.
我们该开个派对庆祝一下启用新的办公室
I think we should have a party for the new offices.
再次向社区介绍自己
Introduce ourselves to the community again.
听上去很棒
That sounds terrific.
好
Good.
我们开吧
Let's do it.
#It's your birthday, happy birthday#
#It's your birthday#
#It's your birthday, it's your birthday#
#It's your birthday, happy birthday#
#It's your birthday happy birthday,#
#it's your birthday #
一切还好吗
How's everything?
很好
Good.
去你的
And fuck you.
#Happy birthday#
#Now, whose birthday is it?#